# **Sergey Zelman**

1-4372260858



sergeyzelman373@gmail.com

LinkedIn

Surrey, BC

# **Full Stack Web Developer**

## Summary

Junior full stack developer just graduated In CDI college with some experience building responsive websites using frontend, backend and database tools like Html5, CSS, JavaScript/TypeScript, node.js, react.js, Java, C#, Python, SQL and NoSQL databases (MySQL and Mongo DB) and more. I am responsible, creative, reliable and good at problem solving.

Have 2 years of experience as a store manager. I was responsible on 30 employees organizing tasks and run business with daily income of 3000-5000 CAD.

3 years military service with certificate of merit.

My hobbies: snowboarding, cooking and playing guitar.

Speak 2 other languages as a native speaker Hebrew and Russian.

#### **Education**

- Web And Mobile Developer Diploma CDI Collage. Burnaby, BC. (2022-2023)
- Truck Driving School Canada Trust Driving School. North York, ON. (2019)
- Professional Chef Certificate Bishulim Collage, Tel-Aviv, Israel. (2016)
- Secondary Education Kfar Saba, Israel. (2005-2008)

## **Work Experience**

- Uber and Lyft Driver Feb 2022 Present. Vancouver, BC.
- Midland Transport May 2019 Nov 2021 Moncton, NB.
- Taavura Trucking Jun 2015 Dec 2019.
- Store Manager Domino's Pizza Israel 2013-2015.
- Domino's pizza Israel 2011-2013.
- Military Service 2008-2011.

#### **Professional Skills**

- Html5, CSS, JavaScript/TypeScript, jQuery, React.js, Node.JS, exspress.js
- **REST API, OOP**
- C# and ASP.Net
- MySQL And Mondo DB
- PHP, Python
- Android and IOS development
- Git and GitHub
- **Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator**
- Word, Excel, PowerPoint